https://esop.li/privacy-policy/

Home › Privacy-PolicyPrivacy-PolicyPrivacy-PolicyBased on this privacy statement, we would like to inform you about how we work with your personal data and explain how we protect it. We have implemented numerous technical organizational measures to ensure the best possible protection of your data. Nevertheless, Internet-based data transmissions can in principle have security gaps, so absolute protection can not be guaranteed. The use of our website is possible in principle without any transmission of personal data. However, if you wish to avail yourself of a service, processing of personal data may be necessary. This occurs, for example, when you send us an e-mail.The processing of your personal data, such as your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number, is always in accordance with the country-specific privacy policy.We would like to point out that our website contains further links to external websites and we have no influence on the processing of data on these sites.Name and contact details of the responsible entity.European Society of Oncology Pharmacy (ESOP)Camille Groos, Treasurer7, rue des ArquebusiersL-1138 LuxembourgLuxembourgPhone:       +49 40 466 5000Fax:            +49 40 466 500 300Email:        membershipservice[at]esop.liSupervisory authorityCommission nationale pour la protection des données1, avenue du Rock’n’RollL-4361 Esch-sur-AlzetteTel.: (+352) 26 10 60-1https://cnpd.public.lu/en.htmlThe information below concerns visits to our website. When visiting our website, no data will be disclosed to third parties.DefinitionsThe privacy statement of the ESOP is based on the terminology used by the European legislature and legislature in adopting the EU General Data Protection Regulation.‘personal data’ means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that individual person;‘processing’ means any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction;‘restriction of processing’ means the marking of stored personal data with the aim of limiting their processing in the future;    ‘processor’ means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes personal data on behalf of the controller;    1‘recipient’ means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or another body, to which the personal data are disclosed, whether a third party or not. 2However, public authorities which may receive personal data in the framework of a particular inquiry in accordance with Union or Member State law shall not be regarded as recipients; the processing of those data by those public authorities shall be in compliance with the applicable data protection rules according to the purposes of the processing;‘controller’ means the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data; where the purposes and means of such processing are determined by Union or Member State law, the controller or the specific criteria for its nomination may be provided for by Union or Member State law;    ‘third party’ means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or body other than the data subject, controller, processor and persons who, under the direct authority of the controller or processor, are authorised to process personal data;Collection of general data and informationWhen you visit our website, data is collected from you and stored in so-called “server log files”. In the following, various data are logged:The visited websiteTime and date of access to our websiteThe browser type and versionThe transmitted amount of dataReport if the access / retrieval of our website was successfulUsed IP addressThese data are only evaluated to ensure and improve the offer and then deleted. A different use of your data or a transfer to third parties does not take place. Top
